http://www.antiquingonline.com/privacy.htm

SERVICE
JOIN OUR MAILINGLIST FOR SITESALES & UPDATES!
Subscribe to RSS Feed
Privacy Statement for Antiquing On LineAntiquing On Line has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your individual privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this site: http://www.antiquingonline.com/  .
Information We Collect and How It's Used
Sharing of Information
Security
Changes
Links
Browser Support
Glossary of Terms
Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart. It is not linked to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous.
Information We Collect and How It's Used
via Order Form:  To process your order, we require your name, billing address, phone number, email address, shipping address and credit card information. We use this information solely to process your order and, if any questions should arise, to contact you about your order. In general, we will try to contact you first by email and only if that fails, or if time is critical, will we try to contact you by phone. We share this information, and only that information which is absolutely necessary, with those third parties that are involved in the processing of your order. For example, the financial institution that issued your credit card and the shipping carrier that delivers your order.
Sharing of Information
Aside from the previously mentioned third parties involved in the processing of your order, we do not share or sell your personal information to anyone.
Security
We utilize industry standard SSL encryption when accepting your credit card information during our online checkout process. With SSL implemented on both the client and server, information sent via the Internet can be trusted to arrive privately and unaltered to our server only. To further enhance our security measures, no credit card information is stored on the server.
Please note that email is not encrypted and is not considered a secure means of transmitting credit card numbers.
Changes in Order information:
To make any changes to your order, please contact us via email. We will be happy to assist you.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. Antiquing On Line is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.
Browser Support:
Enable Cookies
Cookies are not used to track your whereabouts on our site. It is not necessary to have cookies enabled in your browser.
SSL Compatibility
Ordering from our site requires that you are using an SSL-compliant browser.
SSL means Secure Socket Layer.
Basically, you are shopping on a secure site.
Glossary of Terms
IP Address:  When you are connected to the Internet, your computer has a unique Internet ID called an IP address. Most people that connect through a dial-up service
get a different IP address each time they login. Others might have a permanently assigned IP address, called a static IP address. It is difficult or impossible for a web site to collect personal information about
you (i.e., your name, email address, etc.) from your IP address alone, though a static IP address makes this easier.
SSL Encryption:  A method by which information transmitted across the internet is scrambled to the point where it's virtually indecipherable by anyone who should intercept the data before it reaches its destination. Web pages where SSL encryption is activated are typically identified by a lock or key symbol displayed somewhere in your browser. Refer to your browser's documentation for the specific symbol and location.If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact:
Elaine Kula
Antiquing On Line
P.O. Box 7905
Nashua, NH 03060
webmistress@antiquingonline.com
SIGN UP FORSITE SALES & UPDATES!
Gift Ideas
As Seen inVOGUE NIPPON
Like our site?Tell a friend!CLick Here!
©1997- 2014Antiquing On LineAll rights reserved.No part of this web site may be reproduced in any form without prior written authorization.
antique jewelry: [ vintage costume jewelry: (figurals | designer | silver | unsigned | accessories),estate jewelry | 1910 to 1930's | Art Deco jewelry | Victorian & Edwardian jewelry ]antique cameos & antique cameo jewelry archivesvintage jewelry designers: [ A - H | I - Q | R - Z ]about us | bookshelf | comments | contact us | gift registry | help deskjewelrygrams© | other sites |privacy policy | reminder service | requestsguarantee | layaway | ordering | payment | shipping feestop of page | home | site mapAntiquing On LineP.O. Box 7905Nashua, NH
03060USATelephone: 1 603 888 7464Email: webmistress@antiquingonline.comInterested in putting your items for sale on our site?Click here for details.Copyright © 1997-2014 Antiquing On Line.Antique Jewelry, Vintage Costume Jewelry, Victorian Jewelry
